Help on module bikeshare_2:

NAME
    bikeshare_2

FUNCTIONS
    check_answer(ans)
    
    display(df)
    
    get_filters()
        Asks user to specify a city, month, and day to analyze.
        
        Returns:
            (str) city - name of the city to analyze
            (int) month - number corresponding to the name of the month to filter by, or "all" to apply no month filter
            (int) day - number corresponding to the name of the day of week to filter by, or "all" to apply no day filter
    
    load_data(city, month, day)
        Loads data for the specified city and filters by month and day if applicable.
        
        Args:
            (str) city - name of the city to analyze
            (str) month - name of the month to filter by, or "all" to apply no month filter
            (str) day - name of the day of week to filter by, or "all" to apply no day filter
        Returns:
            df - Pandas DataFrame containing city data filtered by month and day
    
    main()
    
    months_in_string(month)
    
    station_stats(df)
        Displays statistics on the most popular stations and trip.
    
    time_stats(df)
        Displays statistics on the most frequent times of travel.
    
    trip_duration_stats(df)
        Displays statistics on the total and average trip duration.
    
    user_stats(df)
        Displays statistics on bikeshare users.

DATA
    CITY_DATA = {'chicago': 'chicago.csv', 'new york city': 'new_york_city...